Guide to the Erwin Cotton Mills records, 1832-1976 and undated, bulk 1892-1967 RL.00366
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Erwin Cotton Mills records
1832-1976 and undated
1892-1967
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Erwin Cotton Mills
RL.00366
156 Linear Feet
357 volumes; 66 boxes; 6 oversize folders.
Account books, nearly complete, and office files, very incomplete, of the Erwin Mills textile mill, chiefly 1892-1967, and some personal papers of William Allen Erwin. The business files include letters, volumes, legal and financial papers, memoranda, printed material, reports, blueprints, and other records of the company.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The records of Erwin Mills, a textile manufacturing company, were gifts and deposits to the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library in 1951, 1955-1956, 1966, and 1987, by Dr. Frank T. de Vyver, Nathaniel Gregory, Erwin Mills, and the J. P. Stevens Company.
Historical Note
Historical Note
1892 Erwin Cotton Mills incorporated, the Duke family owning a controlling interest with Benjamin N. Duke as president and William Allen Erwin as manager.
1893 Mill No. 1 in West Durham began operation
1896 Mill No. 1 doubled in size
1903-1904 Mill No. 2 built at Duke (now Erwin), Harnett Co., N. C.
1906 Colleemee Cotton Mills, Cooleemee, Davie Co., N. C., acquired and operated as Mill No. 3
1909-1910 Mill No. 4, bleachery and finishing plant built in West Durham
1925 Erwin Yarn Company, a selling agency, established in Philadelphia, Pa.
1925-1926 Mill No. 5 built at Erwin, N. C.
1927 William A. Erwin succeeded B. N. Duke as president
1932 Kemp Plummer Lewis succeeded W. A. Erwin as president Pearl Cotton Mills in North Durham acquired and operated as Mill No. 6
1937 Finishing plant added at Cooleemee, N.C.
1947 Erwin Yarn Company liquidated
1948, ca. Diana Mills at Neuse, Wake Co., N. C., acquired and operated as Mill No. 7
1948 William Haywood Ruffin succeeded K. P. Lewis as president Stonewall Cotton Mills, Stonewall, Miss., acquired and operated as Mill No. 8
1949 Accounting procedures changed from longtime standard forms posted by hand to radically different forms utilizing business machines
1950 Company changed name to Erwin Mills
1953 Abney Mills of South Carolina acquired control and its president, Francis Ebenezer Grier, became chairman of the board
1960, ca. Burlington Industries acquired control, Erwin Mills continuing as one of its divisions
1969, ca. Mill No. 6 in North Durham closed
1986 J. P. Stevens acquired and closed West Durham plant
Collection Overview
The records of the Erwin Cotton Mills, a textile manufacturing company, date primarily from 1982-1967 but include items as early as 1832 and as late as 1976. There are ten series: Information; Account Books; Alphabetical; Labor Relations; William Allen Erwin; Pearl Cotton Mills; Cooleemee Cotton Mills; Erwin Yarn company; and J. N. Ledford Company. The collection relates mostly to the company's textile operations and related matters, but there is also some material concerning William A. Erwin's personal and family interests. The account books are largely intact. Most of the correspondence and topical records have not survived and are represented here only by scattered files. Records from the subsidiaries and acquired companies vary but have survived in similar fashion. the Account Books Series and Alphabetical Series comprise the bulk of the collection.
Department stores -- North Carolina; Industries -- North Carolina; Labor and laboring classes -- North Carolina; United States -- Politics and government; North Carolina -- Politics and government; Hunting dogs; Real property -- North Carolina; Architecture -- North Carolina; Textile industry; Durham (N.C.) -- History -- 20th century; Cotton textile industry -- Records; Thomaston Cotton Mills (Thomaston, Ga.); Cooleemee Cotton Mills (Cooleemee, N.C.); Textile Workers Union of America; Alpine Cotton Mills (Morganton, N.C.); Stonewall Cotton Mills (Stonewall, Miss.); St. Mary's Junior College (Raleigh, N.C.); Oxford Cotton Mills (Oxford, N.C.); Erwin, William Allen, 1856-1932; Erwin Yarn Company (Philadelphia, Pa.); Locke Cotton Mills (Concord, N.C.); Erwin Cotton Mills; J.N. Ledford Company (Cooleemee, N.C.); Holt family; Springs Cotton Mills (Lancaster, S.C.); Episcopal Church; Smedes family; Durham Cotton Manufacturing Company (Durham, N.C.); Riverside and Dan River Mills (Danville, Va.); Duke, James Buchanan, 1856-1925; Pearl Cotton Mills (Durham, N.C.); Duke, Benjamin N. (Benjamin Newton); Erwin family
- Information series, undated; 1
  Scope and Contents
  The Information series consists of files of histories produced by the company, along with articles, biographical sketches, and other reference materials from various sources.
  - Reference material (Box 1)
  - Company histories (Box 1)
- Account books series, 1892-1967; 2
  The Account Books series are familiar in form until 1949, when the company stopped posting accounts by hand and began using business machines for its bookkepping. At this point, the ledgers and journals become difficult to interpret, and subsidary records such as the supporting papers for journal entries, voucher registers, check registers, and cash record books can be essential to dating and identifying the numbered ledger books.
  Beginning in 1905, finding particular accounts in the ledgers can be difficult because transfer ledgers were adopted. When a ledger became bulky, account sheets were moved into one or more transfer ledgers with similar dates. This practice produced wide variance in the dates within a particular ledger. Most ledgers are not indexed.
  The company labeled their journals as daybooks until the 1930s, when they adopted the customary terminology of "journal."
  The Exhibit books record quarterly or annual summaries of expenses, income, and profit and loss.
  The Plant ledgers have both technological and architectural interest because they itemize equipment, buildings, and workers' houses, usually with dates of acquisition or construction. These records were begun in 1928 but list assets on hand dating as early as the 1890s.
  "Payroll letters" are quarterly financial summaries of labor expenses; time books, unfortunately, are not included in the collection, meaning workers' names are difficult to obtain. Some names appear elsewhere occasionally, including in the Workmen's Compensation Check Registers, individual rent accounts in some of the ledgers, and in some files of the Alphabetical series.
  - Ledgers, 1892-1967; 1
    - Ledger A, 1892-1900 (Volume 1)
    - Ledger B, 1900-1905 (Volume 2)
    - Index to Ledger B, 1900-1905 (Volume 3)
    - Ledger No. 1, 1905-1910 (Volume 4)
    - Transfer Ledger No. 1 for Ledger No. 1, 1905-1909 (Volume 5)
    - Ledger No. 2, 1911-1929 (Volume 6)
    - Transfer Ledger No. 2 for Ledger No. 2, 1911-1918 (Volume 7)
    - Transfer Ledger No. 2 for Ledger No. 2, 1911-1922 (Volume 8)
    - Transfer Ledger No. 3 for Ledger No. 2, 1911-1928 (Volume 8A)
    - Transfer Ledger No. 4 for Ledger No. 2, 1910-1929 (Volume 9)
    - Operating Ledger No. 4, 1911-1927 (Volume 10)
    - Current Ledger No. 3, 1930-1940 (Volume 11)
    - Transfer Ledger No. 1 for Ledger No. 3, 1930-1936 (Volume 12)
    - Transfer Ledger No. 2 for Ledger No. 3, 1930-1940 (Volume 13)
    - General Ledger No. 4, 1941-1948 (Volume 14)
    - Transfer Ledger No. 1 for Ledger No. 4, 1941-1943 (Volume 15)
    - Transfer Ledger No. 2 for Ledger No. 4, 1941-1946 (Volume 16)
    - Transfer Ledger No. 3 for Ledger No. 4, 1941-1948 (Volume 17)
    - Operating Ledger, 1941-1948 (Volume 18)
    - General Ledger, 1949 (Volume 19)
      Includes journal and cash receipts.
    - General Ledger, 1950 (Volume 20)
      Includes journal, cash receipts, and dividends.
    - General Ledger, 1951 (Volume 21)
      Includes dividends.
    - General Ledger, 1951 Oct.-1952 Sept. (Volume 22)
    - General Ledger, 1952 Oct.-1953 Sept. (Volume 23)
    - General Ledger, 1953 Oct.-1954 Oct. (Volume 24)
    - General Ledger, 1954 Oct.-1955 Sept. (Volume 25)
    - General Ledger, 1955 Oct.-1956 Sept. (Volume 26)
    - General Ledger, 1956 Oct.-1957 Sept. (Volume 27)
    - General Ledger, 1957 Sept.-1958 Sept. (Volume 28)
    - General Ledger, 1958 Sept.-1959 Oct. (Volume 29)
    - General Ledger, 1959 Oct.-1960 Sept. (Volume 30)
    - General Ledger, 1960 Oct.-1961 Sept. (Volume 31)
    - General Ledger, 1961 Oct.-1962 Sept. (Volume 32)
    - General Ledger, 1962 Oct.-1963 Sept. (Volume 33)
    - General Ledger, 1963 Sept.-1964 Oct. (Volume 34)
    - General Ledger, 1964 Oct.-1965 Oct. (Volume 35)
    - General Ledger, 1965 Oct.-1966 Sept. (Volume 36)
    - General Ledger, 1966 Oct.-1967 Sept. (Volume 37)
  - Journals, 1892-1966; 2
    - Journal A, 1892 Apr.-1909 Sept. (Volume 38)
    - Journal B, 1909 Oct.-1913 Aug. (Volume 39)
    - Journal C, 1913 Sept.-1916 Apr. (Volume 40)
    - Journal D, 1916 May-1918 May (Volume 41)
    - Journal E, 1918 June-1920 Mar. (Volume 42)
    - Journal F, 1920 Mar.-1921 Dec. (Volume 43)
    - Journal G, 1921 Dec.-1923 Dec. (Volume 44)
    - Journal H, 1924 Jan.-1926 Apr. (Volume 45)
    - Journal I, 1926 Apr.-1928 Dec. (Volume 46)
    - Journal J, 1928 Dec.-1931 Sept. (Volume 47)
    - Journal K, 1931 Sept.-1935 Dec. (Volume 48)
    - Journal, 1936-1940 (Volume 49)
    - Journal, 1941-1945 (Volume 50)
    - Journal, 1946-1947 (Volume 51)
    - Journal, 1948 (Volume 52)
      Journal entries for 1949-1951 Sept. included in volumes 19-21 with the ledgers during this period.
    - Journal entries, 1951 Oct.-1952 Sept. (Volume 53)
    - Journal entries, 1952 Oct.-1953 Sept. (Volume 54)
    - Journal entries, 1953 Oct.-1954 Oct. (Volume 55)
    - Journal entries, 1954 Oct.-1955 Sept. (Volume 56)
    - Journal entries, 1955 Oct.-1956 Sept. (Volume 57)
    - Journal entries, 1956 Oct.-1957 Sept. (Volume 58)
      Journal entries for 1957-1963 included in volumes 28-33 with the ledgers during this period.
    - Journal entries, 1963 Oct.-1964 Dec. (Volume 59)
      Journal entries for 1965-1967 (3 pages) are in Box 23.
    - Supporting Papers for Journal Entries, 1950 (Volume 60)
      Supporting papers for journal entries for 1949 Jan.-May are in Box 37; for 1949 June-Dec. are in Box 38; for 1949 Dec.-1950 Jan. are in Box 39.
    - Supporting Papers for Journal Entries, 1950 (Volume 61)
    - Supporting Papers for Journal Entries, 1951 Jan.-Sept. (Volume 62)
    - Supporting Papers for Journal Entries, 1951 Feb.-Sept. (Volume 63)
    - Supporting Papers for Journal Entries, 1951 Oct.-1952 Sept. (Volume 64)
    - Supporting Papers for Journal Entries, 1951 Oct.-1952 Sept. (Volume 65)
    - Supporting Papers for Journal Entries, 1952 Oct.-1953 Sept. (Volume 66)
    - Supporting Papers for Journal Entries, 1952 Oct.-1953 Sept. (Volume 67)
    - Supporting Papers for Journal Entries, 1953 Nov.-1954 Oct. (Volume 68)
    - Supporting Papers for Journal Entries, 1953 Nov.-1954 Oct. (Volume 69)
    - Supporting Papers for Journal Entries, 1954 Nov.-1955 Oct. (Volume 70)
    - Supporting Papers for Journal Entries, 1954 Nov.-1955 Oct. (Volume 71)
    - Supporting Papers for Journal Entries, 1955 Oct.-1956 Sept. (Volume 72)
    - Supporting Papers for Journal Entries, 1955 Nov.-1956 Sept. (Volume 73)
    - Supporting Papers for Journal Entries, 1956 Nov.-1957 Sept. (Volume 74)
    - Supporting Papers for Journal Entries, 1956 Nov.-1957 Sept. (Volume 75)
    - Supporting Papers for Journal Entries, 1957 Oct.-1958 Sept. (Volume 76)
    - Supporting Papers for Journal Entries, 1957 Oct.-1958 Sept. (Volume 77)
    - Supporting Papers for Journal Entries, 1958 Oct.-1959 Oct. (Volume 78)
    - Supporting Papers for Journal Entries, 1958 Oct.-1959 Oct. (Volume 79)
    - Supporting Papers for Journal Entries, 1959 Oct.-1960 Sept. (Volume 80)
    - Supporting Papers for Journal Entries, 1959 Nov.-1960 Sept. (Volume 81)
    - Supporting Papers for Journal Entries, 1960 Nov.-1961 Sept. (Volume 82)
    - Supporting Papers for Journal Entries, 1960 Nov.-1961 Sept. (Volume 83)
    - Supporting Papers for Journal Entries, 1961 Nov.-1962 Sept. (Volume 84)
    - Supporting Papers for Journal Entries, 1961 Nov.-1962 Sept. (Volume 85)
    - Supporting Papers for Journal Entries, 1962 Oct.-1963 Sept. (Volume 86)
    - Supporting Papers for Journal Entries, 1962 Oct.-1963 Sept. (Volume 87)
    - Supporting Papers for Journal Entries, 1963 Nov.-1964 June (Volume 88)
    - Supporting Papers for Journal Entries, 1963 Nov.-1964 Oct. (Volume 89)
    - Supporting Papers for Journal Entries, 1964 Oct.-1965 Oct. (Volume 90)
    - Supporting Papers for Journal Entries, 1965 Oct.-1966 Oct. (Volume 91)
  - Trial Balances, 1895-1950; 3
    - Trial Balances, 1895 Dec.-1905 (Volume 92)
    - Trial Balances, 1906-1909 June (Volume 93)
    - Trial Balances, 1909 July-1918 (Volume 94)
    - Trial Balances, 1919-1927 (Volume 95)
    - Trial Balances, 1928-1936 (Volume 96)
    - Trial Balances, 1937-1944 (Volume 97)
    - Trial Balances, 1945-1950 (Volume 98)
  - Exhibits, 1901-1949; 4
    - Exhibits, 1901-1902 (Box 15)
    - Exhibits, 1903 Mar. 31-1908 Sept. 30 (Volume 234)
      Inventory Book 2A, Mill No. 1
    - Exhibits, 1905 Jun. 30-1910 Sept. 30 (Volume 243)
      Inventory Book 1C, Mill No. 2
    - Exhibits, 1910-1916 (Volume 244)
      Inventory Book 2C, Mill No. 2
    - Exhibits, 1908-1911 (Volume 235)
      Inventory Book 3A, Mill No. 1
    - Exhibits, 1911 Mar. 31-1916 Sept. 30 (Volume 99)
    - Exhibits, 1916 Dec. 30-1923 (Volume 100)
    - Exhibits, 1924 Mar. 31-1930 Jun. 30 (Volume 101)
    - Exhibits, 1930 Sept. 30-1934 (Volume 102)
    - Exhibits, 1935 Mar. 30-1940 (Volume 103)
    - Exhibits, 1941 Mar. 31-1949 (Volume 104)
  - Early Statistics, Etc., 1898-1923; 5
    - Statistics, 1898-1906 (Volume 105)
    - Cost Book, 1912-1916 (Volume 106)
    - Price Book No. 1, 1905-1917 (Volume 107)
    - Price Book No. 2, 1917-1920 (Volume 108)
    - Price Book No. 3, 1920-1923 (Volume 109)
  - Cash Record Books, 1897-1967; 6
    - Cashbook B, 1897 May-1900 Dec. (Volume 110)
    - Cashbook C, 1900 Dec.-1903 Nov. (Volume 111)
    - Cashbook D, 1903 Nov.-1906 Mar. (Volume 112)
    - Cashbook E, 1906 Mar.-1908 Jan. (Volume 113)
    - Cashbook F, 1908 Nov.-1909 Oct. (Volume 114)
    - Cashbook G, 1909 Nov.-1911 Feb. (Volume 115)
    - Cashbook H, 1911 Mar.-1912 Apr. (Volume 116)
    - Cashbook I, 1912 May-1913 Aug. (Volume 117)
    - Cashbook J, 1913 Sept.-1914 Dec. (Volume 118)
    - Cashbook K, 1914 Dec.-1916 Mar. (Volume 119)
    - Cashbook L, 1916 Apr.-1917 Jul. (Volume 120)
    - Cashbook M, 1917 Jul.-1918 Oct. (Volume 121)
    - Cashbook N, 1918 Oct.-1919 Dec. (Volume 122)
    - Cashbook O, 1919 Dec.-1921 Apr. (Volume 123)
    - Cashbook P, 1921 Apr.-1922 Aug. (Volume 124)
    - Cashbook Q, 1922 Aug.-1923 Nov. (Volume 125)
    - Cashbook R, 1923 Nov.-1925 Oct. (Volume 126)
    - Cashbook S, 1925 Oct.-1927 Jun. (Volume 127)
    - Cashbook T, 1927 Jun.-1929 Mar. (Volume 128)
    - Cashbook U, 1929 Mar.-1930 Nov. (Volume 129)
    - Cashbook V, 1930 Nov.-1932 Jun. (Volume 130)
    - Cashbook W, 1932 Jun.-1933 Nov. (Volume 131)
    - Cash Receipts No. 1, 1933 Dec.-1937 Dec. (Volume 132)
    - Cash Receipts No. 2, 1938-1940 (Volume 133)
    - Cash Receipts No. 3, 1941-1943 (Volume 134)
    - Cash Receipts No. 4, 1944-1946 (Volume 135)
    - Cash Receipts No. 5, 1947 (Volume 136)
    - Cash Receipts Book No. 1, 1948 (Volume 137)
    - Cash Receipts, 1949-1951 (Volume 19-21)
      Included with volumes 19-21 in the ledgers from this period.
    - Cash Receipts Book No. 3, 1951 Oct.-1952 Sept. (Volume 138)
    - Cash Receipts Book No. 4, 1952 Oct.-1953 Sept. (Volume 139)
    - Cash Receipts Book No. 5, 1953 Oct.-1954 Oct. (Volume 140)
    - Cash Receipts, 1954 Oct.-1955 Sept. (Volume 141)
    - Cash Receipts Book No. 6, 1955 Oct.-1956 Sept. (Volume 142)
    - Cash Receipts Book No. 7, 1956 Oct.-1957 Sept. (Volume 143)
    - Cash Receipts, 1957 Sept.-1963 Sept. (Volume 28-33)
      Included with volumes 28-33 in the ledgers from this period.
    - Cash Receipts Book No. 8, 1963 Oct.-1964 Oct. (Volume 144)
    - Cash Receipts, 1964 Oct.-1965 Oct. (Volume 145)
    - Cash Receipts, 1965 Oct.-1966 Sept. (Volume 146)
    - Cash Receipts, 1966 Oct.-1967 Sept. (Volume 147)
    - Cash Payment Journal, 1933 Dec.-1935 Jun. (Volume 148)
    - Cash Payment Journal, 1935 Jul.-1936 Dec. (Volume 149)
    - Cash Payment Journal, 1937-1938 Jun. (Volume 150)
    - Cash Payment Journal, 1938 Jul.-1939 (Volume 151)
    - Cash Payment Journal, 1940 (Volume 152)
    - Cash Payment Journal, 1941-1942 (Volume 153)
    - Cash Payment Journal, 1943-1944 (Volume 154)
    - Cash Payment Journal, 1945-1946 (Volume 155)
    - Cash Payment Journal, 1947 (Volume 156)
    - Cash Payment Journal, 1948 (Volume 157)
  - Plant Ledgers, 1890s-1964; 7
    - Asset Ledger Index, 1890s-1960s (Volume 158)
      Compiled in the mid-20th century including buildings and equipment, 1890s-1960s. Serves as an index to the plant ledgers but also contains considerable data.
    - Plant Ledger, General Office, 1928-1964 (Volume 159)
    - Plant Ledger, Mills 1 and 4, 1928-1964 (Volume 160)
    - Plant Ledger, Mills 1, 4, 6, 1928-1964 (Volume 161)
    - Plant Ledger, Mills 2 and 5, 1928-1964 (Volume 162)
    - Plant Ledger, Mills 2 and 5, 1928-1964 (Volume 163)
    - Plant Ledger, Mills 7 and 8, 1936-1964 (Volume 164)
    - Plant Ledger, Fully depreciated items, all mills, 1928-1961 (Volume 165)
    - Plant Ledger, Fully depreciated items, General Office and Mills 1, 4, 6, 1928-1964 (Volume 166)
    - Plant Ledger, Fully depreciated items, mostly Mills 2 and 5, 1928-1964 (Volume 167)
    - Plant Ledger, items sold or discarded, 1928-1952 (Volume 168)
    - Plant Ledger, items sold or discarded, 1953-1959 (Volume 169)
    - Plant Ledger, disposals, 1960-1964 (Volume 170)
  - Cotton Records, 1939-1958; 8
    - Cotton Department Purchase Record No. 11, 1939 Sept.-1942 Sept. (Volume 171)
    - Cotton Purchases, Shipments, and Outturns Ledger, 1939-1943 (Volume 172)
    - Cotton Record Book, 1945-1947 Apr. (Volume 173)
    - Cotton Payment Journal for Mills 1, 4, 6, 1947 Sept.-1950 Jan. (Volume 174)
    - Cotton Payment Journal for Mills 2 and 5, 1947 Sept.-1951 Sept. (Volume 175)
    - Cotton Payment Journal for Mill No. 3, 1947 Sept.-1951 Dec. (Volume 176)
    - Cotton Payment Journal for Mills 1, 4, 6, 1950-1953 Apr. (Volume 177)
    - Cotton Payment Journal for Mills 2 and 5, 1951 Sept.-1953 Apr. (Volume 178)
    - Cotton Payment Journal for Mill No. 8, 1948 June-1953 Mar. (Volume 179)
    - Memorandum Cotton Cost Record, 1948-1953 (Volume 180)
    - Memorandum Cotton Cost Record, 1948-1953 (Volume 181)
    - Memorandum Cotton Cost Record, 1948-1953 (Volume 182)
    - Notes Payable and Receivable, 1946-1958 (Volume 183)
  - Voucher Registers, 1949-1964; 9
    - Voucher Register, 1949 Jan.-Jun (Volume 184)
    - Voucher Register, 1949 July-Dec. (Volume 185)
    - Voucher Register, 1950 Jan.-July (Volume 186)
    - Voucher Register, 1950 Aug.-Dec. (Volume 187)
    - Voucher Register, 1951 Jan.-Sept. (Volume 188)
    - Voucher Register, 1951 Oct.-1952 Apr. (Volume 189)
    - Voucher Register, 1952 Apr.-Sept. (Volume 190)
    - Voucher Register, 1952 Oct.-1953 Apr. (Volume 191)
    - Voucher Register, 1953 Apr.-Sept. (Volume 192)
    - Voucher Register, 1953 Oct.-1954 Mar. (Volume 193)
    - Voucher Register, 1954 Apr.-Oct. (Volume 194)
    - Voucher Register, 1954 Oct.-1955 Apr. (Volume 195)
    - Voucher Register, 1955 Apr.-Oct. (Volume 196)
    - Voucher Register, 1955 Oct.-1956 Mar. (Volume 197)
    - Voucher Register, 1956 Mar.-Sept. (Volume 198)
    - Voucher Register, 1956 Oct.-1957 Mar. (Volume 199)
    - Voucher Register, 1957 Mar.-Sept. (Volume 200)
    - Voucher Register, 1957 Oct.-1958 Mar. (Volume 201)
    - Voucher Register, 1958 Mar.-Sept. (Volume 202)
    - Voucher Register, 1958 Oct.-1959 Apr. (Volume 203)
    - Voucher Register, 1959 Apr.-Oct. (Volume 204)
    - Voucher Register, 1959 Oct.-1960 Mar. (Volume 205)
    - Voucher Register, 1960 Mar.-Sept. (Volume 206)
    - Voucher Register, 1960 Oct.-1961 Mar. (Volume 207)
    - Voucher Register, 1961 Mar.-Sept. (Volume 208)
    - Voucher Register, 1961 Oct.-1962 Mar. (Volume 209)
    - Voucher Register, 1962 Mar.-Sept. (Volume 210)
    - Voucher Register, 1962 Oct.-1963 Apr. (Volume 211)
    - Voucher Register, 1963 May-Sept. (Volume 212)
    - Voucher Register, 1963 Oct.-1964 June (Volume 213)
  - Check Registers, 1949-1967; 10
    - Check Register, 1949 (Volume 214)
    - Check Register, 1950 (Volume 215)
    - Check Register, 1951 Jan.-Sept. (Volume 216)
    - Check Register, 1951 Oct.-1952 Sept. (Volume 217)
    - Check Register, 1952 Oct.-1953 Sept. (Volume 218)
    - Check Register, 1953 Oct.-1954 Oct. (Volume 219)
    - Check Register, 1954 Oct.-1955 Sept. (Volume 220)
    - Check Register, 1955 Oct.-1956 Sept. (Volume 221)
    - Check Register, 1956 Oct.-1957 Sept. (Volume 222)
    - Check Register, 1957 Sept.-1958 Sept. (Volume 223)
    - Check Register, 1958 Sept.-1959 Oct. (Volume 224)
    - Check Register, 1959 Oct.-1960 Sept. (Volume 225)
    - Check Register, 1960 Oct.-1961 Sept. (Volume 226)
    - Check Register, 1961 Oct.-1962 Sept. (Volume 227)
    - Check Register, 1962 Oct.-1963 Sept. (Volume 228)
    - Check Register, 1963 Sept.-1964 Oct. (Volume 229)
    - Check Register, 1964 Oct.-1965 Oct. (Volume 230)
      In box with volumes 35-37.
    - Check Register, 1965 Oct.-1966 Sept. (Volume 231)
    - Check Register, 1966 Oct.-1967 Sept. (Volume 232)
  - Inventories, 1893-1967; 11
    - Book 1A, 1893 Dec.-1900 Sept. (Volume 233)
    - Book 2A, Mill 1, 1901 Mar.-1908 Sept. (Volume 234)
      Includes Exhibits 1903-1908.
    - Book 3A, Mill 1, 1908 Dec.-1916 June (Volume 235)
      Includes Exhibits 1908-1911.
    - Book 4A, Mill 1, 1916 Sept.-1921 (Volume 236)
    - Book 5A, Mill 1, 1921 Dec.-1931 (Volume 237)
    - Book 1B, Mill 4, 1911 Mar.-1915 June (Volume 238)
    - Book 2B, Mill 4, 1915 Sept.-1918 (Volume 239)
    - Book 3B, Mill 4, 1919 Mar.-1922 Sept. (Volume 240)
    - Book 4B, Mill 4, 1922 Sept.-1926 (Volume 241)
    - Book 5B, Mill 4, 1927 Dec.-1931 (Volume 242)
    - Book 1C, Mill 2, 1905 Jun.-1910 Sept. (Volume 243)
      Includes Exhibits, 1905-1910.
    - Book 2C, Mill 2, 1910 Dec.-1916 Mar. (Volume 244)
      Includes Exhibit, 1910 Dec. 31.
    - Book 3C, Mill 2, 1916 Jun.-1921 Sept. (Volume 245)
    - Book 4C, Mill 2, 1921 Dec.-1926 Sept. (Volume 246)
    - Book 5C, Mill 2, 1927 Dec.-1931 Dec. (Volume 247)
    - Book 1D, Mill 5, 1925 Dec.-1931 (Volume 248)
    - Book 1E, Mill 3, 1920 Dec.-1925 Jun. (Volume 249)
    - Book 2E, Mill 3, 1925 Sept.-1931 (Volume 250)
    - Mills 2, 3, 5, 7, 8, 1953 Sept. 30 (Volume 251)
    - Mills 1, 4, 6, 1963 Sept. 30 (Volume 252)
    - Mills 3, 7, 8, 1954 Oct. 2 (Volume 253)
    - Mills 1, 2, 4, 5, 6, 1954 Oct. 2 (Volume 254)
    - Mills 2, 3, 5, 7, 8, 1955 Oct. 2 (Volume 255)
    - Mills 1, 4, 6, 1955 Oct. 2 (Volume 256)
    - Mills 3, 7, 8, 1956 Sept. 30 (Volume 257)
    - Mills 1, 2, 4, 5, 6, 1956 Sept. 30 (Volume 258)
    - Mills 1, 4, 6, 1957 Sept. 29 (Volume 259)
    - Mills 2, 3, 5, 7, 8, 1957 Sept. 30 (Volume 260)
    - Mills 1, 2, 4, 5, 6, 1958 Sept. 28 (Volume 261)
    - Mills 3, 7, 8, 1958 Sept. 28 (Volume 262)
    - Mills 3, 8, 1959 Oct. 4 (Volume 263)
    - Mills 1, 2, 4, 5, 6, 1959 Oct. 4 (Volume 264)
    - Mills 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 8, 1960 Oct. 2 (Volume 265)
    - Mills 1, 4, 6, 1961 Oct. 1 (Volume 266)
    - Mills 2, 3, 5, 8, 1961 Oct. 1 (Volume 267)
    - Mills 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 8, 1962 Sept. 29 (Volume 268)
    - Mills 1, 4, 6, 1963 Sept. 29 (Volume 269)
    - Mills 2, 3, 5, 8, 1963 Sept. 29 (Volume 270)
    - Mills 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 8, 1964 Oct. 3 (Volume 271)
      Includes 1965 July 3.
    - Mills 1, 4, 6, 1965 July 3 (Box 19)